Some things are worth more than money.
The Ultimate Life is a drama, romance film directed by Michael Landon Jr..
Despite his best intentions, billionaire Jason Stevens can’t find
enough time to keep his beloved Alexia a priority.
But when he discovers his late grandfather’s journal, he is
transported back to Red Stevens’ incredible world.
With everything he loves hanging in the balance, Jason Stevens
hopes the past will prepare him well for the future.
Jacob Early, played by Peter Fonda.
Ted Hamilton, played by Bill Cobbs.
Alexia, played by Ali Hillis.
Mrs. Hastings, played by Lee Meriwether.
Jason Stevens, played by Logan Bartholomew.
Hobo Joe, played by David Mann.
The Ultimate Life is a 2013 drama film directed by Michael Landon Jr.
and is the sequel to The Ultimate Gift.
It is from a screenplay written by Brian Bird and Lisa G.
Shillingburg, which is in turn based on the best selling novel by Jim Stovall.
It stars Logan Bartholomew, Peter Fonda, and Ali Hillis, and was
released on September 6, 2013 in the United States.
A sequel The Ultimate Legacy was released in 2017.
The film explores themes of hope, inspiration, inspiring.
The tone is uplifting and emotional.